{
    "id": "7423e69837384fa0a5da1e9df3f525a6",
    "title": "Adverb Clause Of Comparison",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is older than ................................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d65e369970fd42b3aa7561fdd2f54c26"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks older than ..............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "she is",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "833de8d2208340b2abd81e297ed782df"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns more money ............................................... me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7117dfc26fde45668cc9703e748f4489"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ............................................. than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more strong",
                "stronger"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3b9e4f20f60414da40723d298b0f9c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are ................................................... than our neighbors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "richer",
                "the richer",
                "the richest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cea6a62e1ff44134813277347df59a3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ............................................. than her sisters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prettiest",
                "prettier"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c48388dbe1f94642a8710eff511942f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He runs ................................................... than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "faster",
                "more fast"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "778b7ff02480431e9611835af9304060"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .............................................. stupid as he is lazy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "as",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d8316c8ce0641dcb7cde84c19a60db5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody loves you more than .............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "I",
                "I do"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c60065868908427dab1e49c826433f97"
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn more than ............................................ does.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "431318d55cce4b53b0fe5d3516dbc07a"
        }
    ]
}